<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>alangerber.us weblog</title><link>http://alangerber.us/blog/</link><description>Recent content on alangerber.us weblog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:39:35 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://alangerber.us/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My First Webapp</title><link>http://alangerber.us/blog/posts/my-first-webapp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:39:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://alangerber.us/blog/posts/my-first-webapp/</guid><description>I built &amp;amp; deployed my first useful webapp over the past week. A friend in with a background in public health teed up a perfectly-sized intro project, a tool to check extended COVID test expiration dates without trawling through PDFs on the FDA website. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a software engineer for years and have wanted to learn how to build frontend UIs for a while, after realizing the relative chaos and churn in that field during the early 2010s seems to have been resolved and the toolchain seems pretty mature.</description></item><item><title>A New Blog</title><link>http://alangerber.us/blog/posts/a-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:09:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://alangerber.us/blog/posts/a-new-blog/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about starting a blog for years, but always got caught in analysis paralysis deciding where and how to do it. I finally put some time into making decisions and actually putting something of my own together while participating in Recurse Center. As a high-level goal, I wanted a simple way to turn Markdown on my computer into a website and blog.
Initially I thought writing my own static site generator could be an enjoyable project, but after scoping out what the project would consist of, I realized it would be a distraction from many other goals like writing words and learning Rust with others and learning about machine learning.</description></item></channel></rss>